The fight starts from inside.
A Prayer Before Dawn is a drama, action, crime film
directed by Jean-Stéphane Sauvaire.
The amazing true story of Billy Moore, an English boxer
incarcerated in Thailand’s most notorious prison.
Thrown into a world of drugs and violence, he finds his best chance to
escape is to fight his way out in prison Muay Thai tournaments.
Billy Moore, played by Joe Cole.
Officer Preecha, played by Vithaya Pansringarm.
Fame, played by Pornchanok Mabklang.
Suthin, played by Somrak Khamsing.
Doctor, played by Nic Shake.
Keng, played by Panya Yimmumphai.
A Prayer Before Dawn is a 2017 biographical prison drama film directed by
Jean-Stéphane Sauvaire and written by Jonathan Hirschbein and Nick Saltrese.
The film stars Joe Cole and is based on the book A Prayer Before
Dawn: My Nightmare in Thailand's Prisons by Billy Moore.
A Prayer Before Dawn had its world premiere at the 2017 Cannes Film Festival on 19 May, and was released in the
United Kingdom on 20 July 2018, by Altitude, and in the United States on 10 August 2018, by A24.
The film explores themes of prison, prisoner, based on
novel or book, thailand, biography.
The tone is emotional.